Guide to the Edwin Richard Weinerman Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, 1945-1970; Series I; 8.5 linear feet (21 boxes)
  - Brassor, Francis P.
    See: box 25, folder 36
  - Braum, Edmund M.
    See: box 14, folder 629
  - Brauner, Erwin Peter (4), 1949 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Brenkman, C. J. (1), 1950 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Brennan, D. S. (2), 1955 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Breslow, Lester (36), 1947, 1952, 1956, 1960, 1962-1964, 1967-1969 (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Breslow, Lester
    See: box 31, folder 114
  - Brewster, Ages W. (40), 1951, 1954-1956, 1960-1965, 1969, undated (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Brewster, Agnes W.
  - Brewster, Kingman, Jr. (99), 1966, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Bridge, Allyn Gustave (2), 1968 (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Brindle, James (38), 1956, 1958-1963, 1965, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Brindle, James
  - British Consulate-General (San Francisco)
    See: box 2, folder 59
  - Brodsky, Harris (5), 1964, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Brooke, Deane F.
  - Brown, Douglas R. (2), 1965 (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Brown, Edmund Gerald (4), 1953, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Brown, Esther Lucille (11), 1951, 1956, 1960-1962, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Brown, Harrison (2), 1960 (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Brown, Howard J. (5), 1956, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Brown, G.O. (2), 1962 (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Brown, John Welch (3), 1948 (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Brown, W.T. (1), 1953 (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Brown, Willard R. (1), 1969 (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Brumm, John M. (34), 1951-1953 (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Brumm, John M. (23), 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - Brush, Marjorie Edwards (5), 1950 (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Bruyn, Henry Bicker (2), 1959 (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Buben, Zdenka (2), 1951 (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Bucove, Bernard (1), 1969 (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Buck, Carl (1), 1949 (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Bull, Roger L. (2), 1969 (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - Bulletin of the Atomic Scientists
    See: box 15, folder 652
  - Bunow, Barry (5), 1962-1963 (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - Burcham, George A. (5), 1950 (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - Burgess, David (1), 1947 (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - Burgess, Eugene (2), 1963 (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - Burke, Thomas J. (3), 1952, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - Burns, Francis J. (2), 1955 (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - Burns, Paul
  - Burroughs, Olive (2), 1955 (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - Bursten, Ben (2), 1964 (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - Burton, Phillip (1), 1960 (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - Butler, Allan Macy (21), 1947, 1951, 1962-1965, 1967-1968, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - C (27), 1946, 1948-1952, 1957, 1961-1964, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 115)
  - California Conference of Social Work (7), 1949, 1951-1952 (Box 4, Folder 116)
  - California Democratic Council (2), 1960 (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - California Federation of Young Democrats (1), 1959 (Box 4, Folder 118)
  - California GP (3), 1959 (Box 4, Folder 118)
  - California Heart Association (2), 1957 (Box 4, Folder 119)
  - California Labor Federation
    See: box 19, folder 846
  - California Labor News Service (1), 1958 (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - California League for Nursing (1), 1956 (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - California League of Nursing Education (1), 1950 (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - California Medical Association (13), 1949-1951, 1953, 1957, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - California Medicine (16), 1949, 1951-1952 (Box 4, Folder 122)
  - California Osteopathic Association (1), 1954 (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - California Society for Crippled Children (1), 1955 (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - California State Department of Education (3), 1949 (Box 4, Folder 124)
  - California State Department of Public Health (8), 1949, 1952, 1956, 1958, 1962, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 125)
  - California State Department of Public Health
  - California State Department of Social Welfare (4), 1961, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 126)
  - California State Employees' Association (2), 1959 (Box 4, Folder 127)
  - California State Nurses' Association (4), 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 127)
  - California State Organization for Public Health Nursing (2), 1950 (Box 4, Folder 127)
  - California Tuberculosis and Health Association (1), 1956 (Box 4, Folder 128)
  - University of California School of Public Health (1), 1955 (Box 4, Folder 128)
  - Californians for the Bill of Rights (1), 1955 (Box 4, Folder 128)
  - Calkins, Charles E. (1), 1947 (Box 4, Folder 129)
  - Callan, Desmond (2), 1969 (Box 4, Folder 129)
  - Cammer, Leonard (3), 1954 (Box 4, Folder 130)
  - Camp, Walter John Richard (1), 1955 (Box 4, Folder 130)
  - Canada, Department of National Health and Welfare (4), 1949-1951 (Box 4, Folder 131)
  - Canadian Medical Association Journal (7), 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 131)
  - Carmean, Mildred (2), 1950 (Box 4, Folder 132)
  - Carmichael, Lynn P. (5), 1967 (Box 4, Folder 132)
  - Carnegie Corporation (4), 1966 (Box 4, Folder 133)
  - Carpendale, M. (1), 1965 (Box 4, Folder 134)
  - Carr, Robert Kenneth
    See: box 15, folder 643
  - Carson, Merl J. (2), 1950 (Box 4, Folder 134)
  - Carstens, Arthur (18), 1950-1953, 1955, 1957, 1961, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 135)
  - Carter, John H. (4), 1963 (Box 4, Folder 136)
  - Carter, Richard (4), 1957-1959 (Box 4, Folder 136)
  - Cashman, John W (3), 1967, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 137)
  - Cath, G.H. (1), 1950 (Box 4, Folder 137)
  - Cattaneo, Everett Grant (2), 1962 (Box 4, Folder 137)
  - Cavallaro, V.J. (1), 1964 (Box 4, Folder 137)
  - Cavanaugh, James H. (1), 1967 (Box 4, Folder 138)
  - "C.B.S. Reports" (2), 1961 (Box 4, Folder 139)
  - Cedars of Lebanon Hospital (Los Angeles, Ca.) (1), 1952 (Box 4, Folder 140)
  - Center for Information on America (3), 1969 (Box 4, Folder 140)
  - Central Manhattan Medical Group (2), 1955 (Box 4, Folder 141)
  - Centre International de L'enfance (3), 1952 (Box 4, Folder 142)
  - Charles, J.A. (1), 1951 (Box 4, Folder 143)
  - Cheever, Francis Sargent (2), 1967 (Box 4, Folder 143)
  - Cherkasky, Martin (22), 1949, 1951-1952, 1954, 1962-1966, 1968, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 144)
  - Chernin, Milton (6), 1948-1949, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 145)
  - Childs, Alfred Wheeler (4), 1966 (Box 4, Folder 146)
  - China Aid Council, Inc. (4), 1947 (Box 4, Folder 146)
  - Chope, Harold D. (2), 1949 (Box 4, Folder 147)
  - Christensen, Carl L. (1), 1961 (Box 4, Folder 147)
  - Cintron, Humberto (2), 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 147)
  - C.I.O. News (4), 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 148)
  - Ciocco, Antonio (2), 1948 (Box 4, Folder 149)
  - Citizens Bank of Pikeville (1), 1960 (Box 4, Folder 149)
  - Citret, Coleman (6), 1950, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 150)
  - Clark, Dean Alexander (25), 1947-1949, 1951-1952, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 151)
  - Clark, Duncan William (2), 1951, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 152)
  - Clark, Thomas Campbell (1), 1946 (Box 4, Folder 152)
  - Clarkson, J. Graham (2), 1969 (Box 4, Folder 152)
  - Clifton, Leon E. (3), 1948-1950 (Box 4, Folder 153)
  - Climan, Max (1), 1946 (Box 4, Folder 153)
  - Cline, John Wesley (1), 1949 (Box 4, Folder 153)
  - Cobb, William Montague (2), 1947 (Box 4, Folder 154)
  - Cohart, Edward Maurice (2), 1967, undated (Box 4, Folder 155)
  - Cohelan, Jeffrey (4), 1950, 1956, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 155)
  - Cohen, Elaine and Seymour (2), 1955 (Box 4, Folder 156)
  - Cohen, Eli (1), 1952 (Box 4, Folder 156)
  - Cohen, Ethel (1), 1949 (Box 4, Folder 157)
  - Cohen, Martin
  - Cohen, Wilbur Joseph (4), 1966, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 157)
  - Coker, William H. (2), 1967 (Box 4, Folder 158)
  - Cole, Richard (3), 1947 (Box 4, Folder 158)
  - Coleman, Jules V. (2), 1965 (Box 4, Folder 158)
  - Collings, G.H. (1), 1953 (Box 4, Folder 159)
  - Collings, Joseph S. (2), 1952 (Box 4, Folder 159)
  - Collins, Selwyn D. (1), 1952 (Box 4, Folder 159)
  - Collins, Vernon (2), 1951 (Box 4, Folder 159)
  - Comerci, George Donald (2), 1968 (Box 4, Folder 160)
  - Commission on Chronic Illness (3), 1950, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 160)
  - Commission on Financing Hospital Care
    See: box 18, folder 821
  - Commission on the Organization of the Executive Branch of Government (Hoover Commission)
  - Committee for the Nations Health
    See: box 3, folder 106 box 5, folder 191 box 15, folder 667 box 18, folder 791
  - Committee of Physicians (22), 1946, 1948-1950, 1952-1953 (Box 4, Folder 161)
  - Committee on Research in Medical Economics
    See: box 5, folder 191
  - Committee to Secure Justice for Morton Sobell
    See: box 18, folder 777
  - Commoner, Barry (6), 1959 (Box 4, Folder 162)
  - Commonwealth Club of California (2), 1949 (Box 4, Folder 163)
  - The Commonwealth Fund
    See: box 47, folder 341
  - Community Health Association of Santa Rosa
    See: box 6, folder 231
  - Community Health Association of Santa Rosa
    See: box 36, folder 203
  - Community Medical Foundation
    See: box 9, folder 343
  - Community Progress, Inc. (4), 1964 (Box 4, Folder 164)
  - Community Welfare Council (1), 1952 (Box 4, Folder 165)
  - Conant, Richard K. (2), 1969 (Box 4, Folder 165)
  - Condon, Robert Likens (1), 1953 (Box 4, Folder 165)
  - Congregation Beth El (2), 1958 (Box 5, Folder 166)
  - Connecticut Medicine
    See: box 14, folder 572
  - Connecticut, University of, School of Medicine
    See: box 18, folder 802
  - Connelly, Douglas (1), 1958 (Box 5, Folder 167)
  - Connors, Helen (5), 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 167)
  - Constance, Lincoln (2), 1956 (Box 5, Folder 168)
  - Consumers' Cooperative Society (4), 1950 (Box 5, Folder 169)
  - Consumers Union (2), 1956, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 170)
  - Contra Costa County Health Department (6), 1951-1952, 1954, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 171)
  - Contra Costa County Heart Association (1), 1954 (Box 5, Folder 171)
  - Contra Costa County Medical Association
    See: box 1, folder 15
  - Contra Costa County Schools (2), 1958 (Box 5, Folder 171)
  - Contra Costa County Social Service Department (1), 1950 (Box 5, Folder 171)
  - Cook, Charles D. (1), 1964 (Box 5, Folder 172)
  - Cooley, George W.(1), 1952 (Box 5, Folder 172)
  - Cooper, Joseph David (2), 1968 (Box 5, Folder 172)
  - Cooper, Ruth (1), 1949 (Box 5, Folder 172)
  - Cooperative Health Federation of America
  - Cooperative Health Insurance Plan of Milwaukee (7), 1953 (Box 5, Folder 173)
  - Cooperative Health Insurance Plan of Milwaukee (22), 1954-1955 (Box 5, Folder 174)
  - Cope, J. Raymond
    See: box 6, folder 258
  - Copperman, Michael
  - Cornell University (4), 1949, 1951, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 175)
  - Cornely, Paul B. (10), 1957-1958, 1963, 1965, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 176)
  - Coro Foundation (3), 1960 (Box 5, Folder 177)
  - Cosin, Lionel Z. (2), 1967 (Box 5, Folder 177)
  - Council of Social Agencies of Syracuse and Onondaga County (2), 1950 (Box 5, Folder 177)
  - Covitz, Martin (2), 1962 (Box 5, Folder 178)
  - Cowan, Carole (2), 1968 (Box 5, Folder 178)
  - Craig, Homer (4), 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 179)
  - Crede, Robert Henry (3), 1965 (Box 5, Folder 179)
  - Crew, Francis A.E. (2), 1950 (Box 5, Folder 180)
  - Norbert Cronin and Co. (3), 1952 (Box 5, Folder 180)
  - Crosby, Edwin L. (3), 1949 (Box 5, Folder 181)
  - Crosby, Roy C. (5), 1949 (Box 5, Folder 181)
  - Cross, Charles O.
    See: box 18, folder 782
  - Cruikshank, Nelson
    See: box 1, folder 26
  - Crutchfield, James A. (1), 1949 (Box 5, Folder 182)
  - Cumming, Gordon (1), 1960 (Box 5, Folder 182)
  - Cunningham, Kathleen (2), 1949 (Box 5, Folder 182)
  - Cunningham, Robert M.
    See: box 13, folder 552
  - Cutter Laboratories (1), 1955 (Box 5, Folder 183)
  - Cutting, Cecil Cooper (5), 1960-1961 (Box 5, Folder 183)
  - Cynamon, Michael (4), 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 184)
  - D (20), 1948-1951, 1955-1956, 1962-1965, 1967-1969 (Box 5, Folder 185)
  - Daily, Edwin F. (26), 1950-1953, 1960, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 186)
  - Daley, Richard J.
    See: box 18, folder 786
  - Daniels, Henry C. (4), 1955, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 187)
  - Daniels, Henry C.
  - Dartmouth Medical School
    See: box 18, folder 804
  - David, Will (2), 1969 (Box 5, Folder 188)
  - Davies, Dean F. (2), 1965 (Box 5, Folder 188)
  - Davis, Aubrey, Jr. (2), 1952, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 189)
  - Davis, Burnet M. (2), 1964 (Box 5, Folder 189)
  - Davis, Horace Bancroft (1), 1954 (Box 5, Folder 190)
  - Davis, Louis (7), 1958, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 190)
  - Davis, Michael Marks (30), 1947-1951 (Box 5, Folder 191)
  - Davis, Michael Marks, 1955, 1958-1959, 1961-1962, 1966, 1968-1970 (Box 5, Folder 192)
  - Michael M. Davis Lectureship Fund (5), 1961, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 193)
  - Dearing, Warren Palmer
  - Degnan, George (3), 1960, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 194)
  - DeKruif, Alice D. (1), 1951 (Box 5, Folder 194)
  - DeKruif, Paul (1), 1951 (Box 5, Folder 194)
  - de Laet, M. (2), 1950 (Box 5, Folder 194)
  - de Lappe, Russell G. (2), 1951 (Box 5, Folder 194)
  - Delta Omega (9), 1948-1951 (Box 5, Folder 195)
  - Democratic Central Committee of Contra Costa County (1), 1954 (Box 5, Folder 196)
  - Denhez, Julien (2), 1969 (Box 5, Folder 196)
  - Denoyer-Geppert Company (4), 1950, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 197)
  - Derry, John Robert (3), 1946-1947 (Box 5, Folder 198)
  - De Silva, Joseph T. (14), 1950, 1951, 1953-1954 (Box 5, Folder 199)
  - Deuschle, Kurt W. (2), 1968 (Box 5, Folder 200)
  - Deutsch, Albert (16), 1946-1948, 1951, 1953, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 201)
  - Development and Resources Corporation (2), 1958 (Box 5, Folder 202)
  - Disney, Walt (1), 1955 (Box 5, Folder 203)
  - Doctors Committee to Give Medical Aid to Strikers and Families (2), 1951 (Box 5, Folder 204)
  - Dodd, Thomas Joseph (4), 1965 (Box 5, Folder 205)
  - Dolinsky, Edward M. (7), 1951, 1960, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 206)
  - Dollar, Melvin (1), 1950 (Box 5, Folder 207)
  - Domke, Herbert R. (1), 1949 (Box 5, Folder 207)
  - Donabedian, Avedis (7), 1964-1965, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 208)
  - Donald, William Goodricke (1), 1951 (Box 5, Folder 209)
  - Doran, William T. (2), 1952 (Box 5, Folder 209)
  - Dorsey, John Morris (3), 1949 (Box 5, Folder 209)
  - Douglas, Bruce L. (1), 1962 (Box 5, Folder 210)
  - Draper, Warren Fales (2), 1950 (Box 5, Folder 210)
  - Drolet, G.J. (2), 1952 (Box 5, Folder 211)
  - Drug Topics, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 211)
  - Dublin, Thomas David (15), 1948-1950 (Box 5, Folder 212)
  - Du Bois, Donald W. (2), 1965 (Box 5, Folder 213)
  - Duester, Mathilda (1), 1965 (Box 5, Folder 213)
  - Duff, Raymond S. (2), 1968 (Box 5, Folder 214)
  - Duffy, Benedict J. (6), 1961-1962, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 214)
  - Dugan, David (2), 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 215)
  - Duke, Marie (2), 1956 (Box 5, Folder 215)
  - Duncan, Faiga Fram (6), 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 215)
  - Duncombe, Dave (2), 1968 (Box 5, Folder 216)
  - Dusheck, George (4), 1949, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 216)
  - Dyar, Robert (2), 1949 (Box 5, Folder 216)
  - Dyke, Frank van (2), 1965 (Box 5, Folder 217)
  - E (13) (Box 6, Folder 218)
  - Eagle, J. Frederick (1) (Box 6, Folder 219)
  - Earnshaw, Katherine
  - Ebbert, Arthur, Jr. (2), 1962 (Box 6, Folder 219)
  - Ebert, Robert Higgins (1), 1965 (Box 6, Folder 220)
  - Ebert, Robert Higgins
  - Eckhert, George L. (2), 1967 (Box 6, Folder 220)
  - Eddison, Grace Gere (2), 1968 (Box 6, Folder 220)
  - Eden, Philip (3), 1963 (Box 6, Folder 221)
  - Edises, Bertram (3), 1961 (Box 6, Folder 221)
  - Egeberg, Roger O. (2), 1969 (Box 6, Folder 222)
  - Eichorn, Robert L. (3), 1969 (Box 6, Folder 222)
  - Albert Einstein College of Medicine
    See: box 16, folder 692
  - Eisenhower, Dwight David (2), 1955 (Box 6, Folder 223)
  - Elgosin, Richard B. (3), 1964, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 224)
  - Eliot, Martha May (2), 1948 (Box 6, Folder 224)
  - Elling, Raymond H. (8), 1966, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 225)
  - Elliot, James S. (2), 1955 (Box 6, Folder 226)
  - Ellsworth, Ted (22), 1955-1957, 1959-1962, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 227)
  - Elsom, Katharine O'Shea (4), 1955, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 228)
  - Emerson, Haven (3), 1953 (Box 6, Folder 228)
  - Emerson, Luther Lee (3), 1969 (Box 6, Folder 229)
  - Endsley, Mildred (5), 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 229)
  - Engle, Clair (6), 1959-1961 (Box 6, Folder 230)
  - Epstein, Frederick Merton (31), 1962-1970 (Box 6, Folder 231)
  - Epstein, Monroe (1), 1950 (Box 6, Folder 232)
  - Erickson, Robert J. (1), 1960 (Box 6, Folder 232)
  - Errebo-Knudsen, E.O. (2), 1954 (Box 6, Folder 232)
  - Esselstyn, Caldwell B. (18), 1962-1968 (Box 6, Folder 233)
  - Esson, William B. (2), 1962 (Box 6, Folder 234)
  - Esson, William B.
  - Etkins, Seymour (2), 1949 (Box 6, Folder 235)
  - Eubanks, Mary (3), 1958 (Box 6, Folder 235)
  - Evang, Karl (8), 1958, 1967-1968, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 236)
  - [Evans?], Betty (1), 1961 (Box 6, Folder 237)
  - Evans, David (4), 1946, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 238)
  - Evans, Lester J. (5), 1951, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 238)
  - Ewell, John Woodruff (1), 1967 (Box 6, Folder 239)
  - Ewing, Oscar Ross (2), 1950 (Box 6, Folder 239)
  - Excerpta Medica (11), 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 240)
  - F (20), 1948-1952, 1955-1956, 1960, 1962, 1964, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 241)
  - Faber, Garold (2), 1962 (Box 6, Folder 242)
  - Fabro, J. Alfred (2), 1962 (Box 6, Folder 242)
  - Fairley, Lincoln
  - Falk, Isidore Sydney (13), 1945-1949, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 243)
  - Falk, Isidore Sydney (37), 1958-1968 (Box 6, Folder 244)
  - Falk, Leslie Alan (30), 1946-1948 (Box 6, Folder 245)
  - Falk, Leslie Alan (37), 1949-1951 (Box 6, Folder 246)
  - Falk, Leslie Alan (26), 1952-1953, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 247)
  - Falk, Leslie Alan (29), 1958-1961 (Box 6, Folder 248)
  - Falk, Leslie Alan (9), 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 249)
  - Falk, Leslie Alan (33), 1964-1966, 1969-1970, undated (Box 6, Folder 250)
  - Falk, Leslie Alan
    See: box 34, folder 171 box 34, folder 160
  - Falls, Caroline (4), 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 251)
  - Farrisey, Claire (3), 1962, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 251)
  - Federal Personnel Council of San Francisco (3), 1949 (Box 6, Folder 252)
  - Federation for Repeal of the Levering Act (4), 1951-1952 (Box 6, Folder 252)
  - Feingold, Al (1), 1952 (Box 6, Folder 253)
  - Feinstein, Alvan Richard (2), 1963 (Box 6, Folder 253)
  - Feise, Richard (1), 1960 (Box 6, Folder 253)
  - Feise, Richard (Centerville Clinic)
    See: box 34, folder 160
  - The Fellowship of Humanity (2), 1953, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 254)
  - Felton, [Jean Spencer?] (5), 1950, 1952, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 254)
  - Ferguson, Thomas (2), 1950-1951 (Box 6, Folder 255)
  - Ferrier, Thompson A. (7), 1961-1962, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 255)
  - Ferrier, Thompson A.
  - Fine, Alvin I. (10), 1960 (Box 6, Folder 256)
  - Fine, Jacob (2), 1969 (Box 6, Folder 257)
  - Fink, Donald L. (2), 1965 (Box 6, Folder 257)
  - Finley, Joanne E.
  - First Unitarian Church, Berkeley (2), 1953, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 258)
  - First Unitarian Church, Los Angeles (18), 1953-1954, 1956, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 258)
  - First Unitarian Church, San Francisco (1), 1956 (Box 6, Folder 258)
  - Fischer, Steve (4), 1951 (Box 7, Folder 259)
  - Fishbein, Morris
    See: box 1, folder 34
  - George B. Fisher Co. (2), 1946 (Box 7, Folder 260)
  - FitzGibbon, J.P. (5), 1949, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 260)
  - Fitzsimmons, Robert J. (2), 1964 (Box 7, Folder 261)
  - Flash, William S. (5), 1952, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 261)
  - Fleeson, William (1), 1965 (Box 7, Folder 262)
  - Fleischner, Felix G. (2), 1946 (Box 7, Folder 262)
  - Fleishman, Joel L. (2), 1968 (Box 7, Folder 262)
  - Fleming, Arthur (1), 1960 (Box 7, Folder 263)
  - Florio, Lloyd (3), 1950-1951 (Box 7, Folder 263)
  - Flynn, Edward J. (2), 1951 (Box 7, Folder 263)
  - Fogh, Jorgen (7), 1953 (Box 7, Folder 264)
  - Follmann, J.F. (3), 1961, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 265)
  - Foote, Franklin Manley (1), 1964 (Box 7, Folder 265)
  - Foregger, Richard (1), 1951 (Box 7, Folder 265)
  - Forsythe, Warren Ellsworth (2), 1949 (Box 7, Folder 266)
  - Foster, John T. (1), 1968 (Box 7, Folder 266)
  - Foster, Katharine D. (2), 1970 (Box 7, Folder 266)
  - Fountain, J.H. (2), 1950 (Box 7, Folder 267)
  - Fox, Lewis (3), 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 267)
  - Fraenkel, Osmond K. (1), 1960 (Box 7, Folder 267)
  - Frank, Howard A. (3), 1953 (Box 7, Folder 268)
  - Fransden, J. (1), 1950 (Box 7, Folder 268)
  - Freedberg, A. Stone (6), 1958, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 269)
  - Freedman, Donald Kenneth (26), 1947-1949, 1951, 1959, 1961, 1963, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 270)
  - French, David Marshall (2), 1966 (Box 7, Folder 271)
  - French, Fern. E. (1), 1965 (Box 7, Folder 271)
  - Frese, Donald B. (3), 1966 (Box 7, Folder 271)
  - Friedman, David Belais (5), 1952, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 272)
  - Friedman, Jay W. (3), 1963 (Box 7, Folder 272)
  - Friedman, Julian (2), 1962-1963 (Box 7, Folder 272)
  - Friends Committee on Legislation
    See: box 18, folder 818
  - Fritchman, Stephen H.
  - Frontier (8), 1954, 1960, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 273)
  - Frost, David (6), 1960, 1964-1966 (Box 7, Folder 274)
  - Fry, John (1), 1967 (Box 7, Folder 274)
  - Fuchs, Jesse (2), 1952 (Box 7, Folder 275)
  - Funt, Dorothy (2), 1963 (Box 7, Folder 275)
  - Furniss, J.B.
    See: box 19, folder 832
  - Furniture Workers Welfare Fund (2), 1960 (Box 7, Folder 275)
  - Furst, Joseph B. (2), 1949 (Box 7, Folder 275)
  - Furstenberg, Frank Folke (18), 1959-1962, 1964-1965, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 276)
  - G (35), 1946-1954, 1960, 1962-1968, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 277)
  - Galdston, Iago (5), 1952 (Box 7, Folder 278)
  - Gans, David S. (2), 1965 (Box 7, Folder 279)
  - Gans, Stephen (1), 1951 (Box 7, Folder 279)
  - Gardipee, Charles (1), 1960 (Box 7, Folder 280)
  - Garfield, Sidney R. (2), 1950 (Box 7, Folder 280)
  - Gaster, Joseph (2), 1954-1955 (Box 7, Folder 281)
  - Gates, Kermit H. (4), 1949 (Box 7, Folder 281)
  - Gaulden, Edmund C. (1), 1963 (Box 7, Folder 282)
  - Gebhard, Bruno (3), 1952 (Box 7, Folder 282)
  - Geiger, Herman Jack (1), 1966 (Box 7, Folder 283)
  - Gennis, Joseph (2), 1968 (Box 7, Folder 283)
  - Gentry, John Tilmon (5), 1959, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 284)
  - Gerber, Joseph (1), 1949 (Box 7, Folder 285)
  - Geriatrics (2), 1968 (Box 7, Folder 285)
  - Getting, Vlado Andrew (8), 1948, 1951-1952 (Box 7, Folder 285)
  - Giamo, Robert Nicholas (10), 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 286)
  - Gibson, Count (2), 1968 (Box 7, Folder 287)
  - Gibson, Luther (1), 1960 (Box 7, Folder 287)
  - Gibson, Richard M. (2), 1951-1952 (Box 7, Folder 287)
  - Gibson, William C. (1), 1953 (Box 7, Folder 287)
  - Gilbert, Robert Alfred (2), 1965 (Box 7, Folder 288)
  - Gill, Sterling (5), 1951-1952, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 288)
  - Gladstone, Betty
    See: box 33, folder 157
  - Glaser, Robert Joy (4), 1965 (Box 7, Folder 289)
  - Glass, D.V. (1), 1950 (Box 7, Folder 290)
  - Glasser, Melvin A. (4), 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 291)
  - Glazier, William H. (14), 1946, 1950-1951, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 292)
  - Gleason, Marion (2), 1950 (Box 7, Folder 293)
  - Glenn, Michael Lyon (3), 1966 (Box 7, Folder 293)
  - Glogow, Eli (7), 1952-1953, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 294)
  - Godfrey, Arthur (1), 1959 (Box 7, Folder 295)
  - Goerke, Lenor Stephen (2), 1960, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 295)
  - Goldberg, Theodore (3), 1963, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 296)
  - Goldenthal, Carol (2), 1956 (Box 7, Folder 296)
  - Goldmann, Franz (23), 1946-1950 (Box 7, Folder 297)
  - Goldmann, Franz (35), 1951-1953, 1955-1957, 1961-1965, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 298)
  - Goldsmith, John (1), 1950 (Box 8, Folder 299)
  - Goldsmith, Sadja (2), 1961 (Box 8, Folder 299)
  - Goldstein, Avram Shalom (21), 1945-1948, 1950-1951, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 300)
  - Goldstein, David N.
  - Goldstein, George S. (24), 1952, 1955, 1959-1963, 1966, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 301)
  - Goldstein, Marcus S. (9), 1950-1952, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 302)
  - Goldwater, Leonard John (10), 1948, 1950-1952 (Box 8, Folder 303)
  - Gonnerman, Alice (4), 1965 (Box 8, Folder 304)
  - Gonnerman, Alice
  - Gordon, Hyman H. (3), 1951-1952 (Box 8, Folder 305)
  - Gordon, J. King (1), 1946 (Box 8, Folder 305)
  - Gordon, John Everett (11), 1948-1949, 1951-1954, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 306)
  - Gordon, Margaret S. (2), 1961 (Box 8, Folder 307)
  - Gorman, Michael (1), 1952 (Box 8, Folder 307)
  - Gottschalk, Patricia S. (2), 1961 (Box 8, Folder 307)